there's only one
day
remaining
on the countdown clock which means i
actually need to finish all the
preparations for the rv
that machine is still going
i have been interrupted about three
times
this machine is probably the most
annoying thing especially as i've torn
apart these trees i can't find them
they're definitely not in the trees it's
got to be underground forget it i'm not
bothered that stupid machine can just
stay where it is however we have only
got one day remaining until the rv
happens so i need to cover up this
countdown because it's actually stayed
in this um bare state for a while which
is uh not great to be honest with you it
it shouldn't look like this we need to
hippie fi a lot of these things
but speaking of the countdown clock
impulse has also done me a huge favor he
has saved this build big time he's
connected all of this stuff up it all
feeds itself with a bone meal and it
feeds all of those things into the giant
storage system here so we've got loads
of green dot like a lot of green dye and
then the sugar cane a lot of sugar cane
and then we got bone meal which is
steadily making its way
up through the system but anyway let's
crack on with building this cover it
shouldn't take too long because i've got
all of the materials i need somewhere
around
here in my chest monster right here we
go so in our first time laps there's
going to be three in this episode i
believe we are going to be covering up
this rather iron heavy redstone block
floating in the sky now i'm not gonna
spend too long on it but i am just gonna
make it a little bit more natural with a
few bits of spruce trap doors and of
course making sure that it's not
floating so it's actually being held up
but i also don't want it to take up too
much space i think i've done all right
well i did just put it in a big wooden
box but it definitely looks better than
the flying monstrosity that was the
redstone beforehand but i think that
actually looks pretty decent it's
definitely just served a purpose of
letting people know that there is only
one day
left what i didn't really think about
is um the redstone
activates the trap doors look look what
happens if i increase the number on this
side some of the trapdoors go
and it just depends on what number it is
i don't think it breaks it at all but
depending on the number you get
different trap doors opening which kind
of reveals the redstone anyway i didn't
think that one through i'm afraid but
seeing as there's only one day left it's
not really a big deal so i've covered up
this redstone i now need to cover up all
this redstone and as you can see i've
kind of been planning out this big barn
shape
but i noticed that someone has left me a
lot of signs
this is a bit of a dig iskall could have
just left me a book instead he put lots
of signs dear green i don't know why
he's shouting sahara is in need of lots
of different he he just put one word on
each side dies
all colors except black can you help out
iskal85 yeah he's just taking the mick
right well the thing is
um
i'm busy i can't actually get the dies
for him right now because
this machine is serving a purpose i need
it for the giant launch
so
i'm gonna pop over to his base real
quick and i'm gonna leave him a message
of my own he'll understand i don't know
how i'm doing this i'll be honest
i'm flying through
ow
now i'm crawling
this girl's base is like 10 million
miles away
i've only ever been here once and it
looks like it's changed quite a lot jeez
iskall
going at it what is this i don't really
know where to leave some signs so i'm
just gonna pop them right here
i've left this message hi isk
al i'm afraid i can't get dyes right now
because i'm busy being a hippie with ren
trying to get back my time machine and
launch a giant rv into space
normal day on the hermitcraft server
when i've saved a villager with my head
on
i will maybe get some dyes for you okay
bye
when i actually wrote all that down i
then realized how insane this story has
become
am i really trying to get a time machine
back and launching an rv into space
okay let's do the long journey back
to
hermit land
this is gonna be a long ride
this time thankfully i've got a boat
it's taking me a while to ride this
tunnel think how long it took to make
this tunnel
very long
and we're finally back i wonder if we've
sold any more memberships it's unlikely
as we've already sold eight in total
no no more okay we're finally back in
the area
and
you know what i've never actually
checked out what's going on over here in
this town i've kind of just let them do
their own thing because they've kind of
got nothing to do with the hippies i
don't really know what they've been up
to but this i saw the other day and now
it's a crop circle how cool is this
pattern they are really going in for
this area 77 theming i love it let's
take a little mosey around i've never
actually had a look alien museum coming
soon awesome area 77 tour guide are they
offering tours and then there's like a
bar or something in here doesn't look
very finished they got an ice cream
truck oh that is so cute this place is
pretty cool now if they're offering some
tours
maybe ren and i can get a little bit of
inside information like
we've been pretty scared to go inside
this area because if we get caught
oh goodness like that machine again if
we get caught we're in big trouble but
if we go on an official tour
then we can get a good look around
without fear of getting in trouble
hmm that might be really good anyway
what i need to do now is gonna take me a
while but i need to build this barn
because i you saw in my last episode
that i had to open up this
wall so
they've actually had a good opportunity
to look inside so i want to get this
wall up and running again and i need to
build this barn so we got another time
lapse to do
let's get it done
oh boy this is a really quite a long
time lapse so all of this redstone needs
covering up ren was on my case about how
ugly this looked so i needed to make
this more
you know hippie-like but
covering it up in a hippy way i couldn't
think of anything big enough so i
decided to go more for like the farmer
angle and then i looked up some big
american style barns and i saw these big
red barns and i thought maybe i could
just cover it in one of those however
the shape was so peculiar how it wasn't
one perfect rectangle i kind of had to
improvise on the design quite a lot and
instead of going for a really bright red
concrete it decided to go for the
slightly lighter
terracotta and i think it has worked out
indeed but this was a lot more resources
than i anticipated so i had to make a
couple of trips over to the mesa and i
had to go and find some birch logs from
somewhere as well overall i think this
is good i didn't bother detailing the
back side of the wall or the two sides
because as you can see there's lots of
saplings now growing because i'm
replacing the big wall that was once
there so i really didn't see the point
in spending too much time detailing but
the front of it looks absolutely spot on
what i wanted it to look like obviously
no barn looks like that because it's
just far too complex and big but i think
it works and i love how this hippie land
is coming together
this looks absolutely brilliant well
it's not exactly hippie is it but this
is an organic farm now and i kind of
like how the hippie area
it's a real mixed bag we got some rvs we
got an organic farm and then we've got
some mushrooms and tents and then we've
got the giant barn not to mention the
giant rv
but this has worked out pretty well i've
got it all nicely labeled it's nice and
bold
this is how everyone should be
decorating their farms it's awesome okay
so let's pop these all on and see if it
works
if you want to take a look under the
hood
we've got to go inside
yeah this is loud in theory this should
be producing a lot of things i've got
all of the farms running
i can see all the flowers being produced
everything should be working so let's
take a quick look
yes we can see that the poppies are
filling up
ah
there's entity build up there's there's
too much going through at once that's
not good
so this farm really isn't designed to
have everything on at once i've got to
i've got to just put them on as they are
needed i think but honestly this thing
is awesome this is the first machine
i've ever made and i'm happy with the
build
you know everything looks pretty cool
however i do need a slight break from
the redstone and the building because
it's been pretty intense already i've
built this thing and i've built this
thing
and it's a couple of projects well done
you might have noticed this little glass
box over here this is for pillagers so
if we see a patrol anywhere it's all
hands on deck and getting those pillages
however i really do as i say need a
break so i think i'm actually gonna head
to the mini game district and give some
games a go iskall has been pestering me
to play his minigame because he thinks
that i'll i'll do well at it or i'll get
addicted i don't know we're gonna find
out what it's all about though
put a diamond in here okay
let's just let's just go
oh okay we're in and now i continue
walking uh
i think that's a loss this girl has
actually explained this game to me so
you put a diamond in here and then it's
basically mostly a game of chance
so there's a chance that the door will
open or in my case not open and i'm
getting very unlucky
iskall iscow
three in a row
there we go
oh i made it
okay i'm gonna take i'm gonna take the
tag
yeah i got a key okay so you got to
collect the keys on this mini game
that's the whole point you have to
collect the keys and then at the end
what you can do is take them over there
and then you can exchange the keys for
some goodies so that's what we're going
to do we're going to spend all of these
diamonds
until we get a bunch of keys and we're
going to see if we can get our luck
i am having the worst luck already
come on gimme
go i almost made it to the end as well
all right we're at the second level now
oh
okay
uh
this one's a parkour
do i risk it yeah i'm gonna risk it
let's do it
oh man
so i just gotta wait for the timing to
be absolutely perfect and then i'm gonna
go for it this may take a while
i'll go for it
i made it okay but one more it's taking
a while for the opportunity to present
itself
go for it
oh i made it
is that it i made it to the end
[Music]
yes
okay how many do we get five keys
nice
yes that's really good okay we've got
five keys
so i'm only really after the jackpot so
every time we win we should definitely
just go and try our luck in the
roulette thing i guess okay here we go
how does this work
one of these oh this is so exciting
do i win anything
ah
a box for linda still a box full of dirt
isn't necessarily bad i get a shulker
box as well that's not too bad okay okay
okay okay we got five more to do can i
do more than one at the same time i
don't really know how it works one key
at a time
here we go
the suspense
i like this i like this little tune
super poop
they made a little face out of rubbish
well i still get i still get a shulker
box i suppose but super poop
come on just gotta keep trying
right
four more left
come on come on
super jackpot
that looks good that's a good color
rare okay okay i'm not complaining i
could you i could always use more
fireworks that's awesome okay
right we got we got some more
this is well worth it i mean i spent i
spent a few diamonds i spent like 10
diamonds i think most of them just went
on the first one
come on
give me a good one
give me a good box give me a good box
common
[Music]
that looks common hey that's not too bad
lighting is always good
you know for 10 diamonds i'm not doing
too bad even i couldn't get this many
shulker boxes for 10 diamonds i don't
think iskal's done the maths on this
this must cost him so much well i i
guess i got kind of lucky i spent well i
spent like 12 diamonds i think all right
last key
we're gonna keep playing this until we
get the big jackpot i tell you
go on
yes
we got the mega
jackpot dude that's the manual yes the
last key
oh my goodness look at all this how many
diamonds is that
how much profit have we just made
holy
smokes oh my goodness
take that super poop look at all these
diamonds
we made just under three stacks of
diamonds from this oh my god oh my heart
oh my heart iscal that was so awesome i
to be honest with you i failed an awful
lot in this game because
the amount of times that i i put a
diamond in and then it just went
let me in might as well do it and then i
fell through this one
no i'm getting lucky and then i get
knocked yeah
that happens quite a lot and then you
just gotta go back
but instead of just showing you every
single fail i decided to just get get
myself to the green room i don't think
there's any point in playing anymore
because i've got the mega jackpot and
that's really what i was after
nope see lost another one okay okay
i don't know if you can jump through
this
no
come on come on that happens so often
it's such a game of chance but
then again i did just i did just do very
very well i had six keys in total and i
got the mega jackpot i am so happy with
that so so so happy with that there's
another shop that's turned up here as
well the xp me
xp me
why is cub's eyes blacked out
the heck and why is he wearing a suit it
would be more effective if he wasn't
wearing bright blue
diamond armor
he's just he's just staring me out what
is he doing
is he one of them now
why is he giving me diamonds
i am so confu
oh
i've just been paid off i saw nothing
i mean if he wants to give me six
diamonds he wants to give me six
diamonds i'm not gonna say anything you
guys you guys aren't gonna say anything
right i i didn't see anything he's
definitely not he's yeah he's even he's
even got sunglasses on the tablet well
i'm not gonna say anything i'll keep my
mouth shut i'm gonna use these six
diamonds to buy me some more golden
carrots and after all of those
shenanigans and after all of these
builds
it's actually hit
day
zero it's time for the rv
to finally
launch so i need to get impulse here
because i don't really know how his
clock works it needs to like be set on a
timer or something because we need to
like do a countdown to launch like nine
eight seven six five et cetera
i'm so ready okay i'm ready it's time to
get this launched let me get hold of
impulse and then we're going to send
this thing
well you'll see
impulse
what's up green it is launch day
zero on the timer
oh my gosh i am excited man we've been
waiting for this day for a long time i
am super ready but uh what where's ren
at oh ren's right here oh
there he is oh he was behind you i
didn't even see him there they needed
too many organic beetroot instead of
real nutrition huh
yeah he's looking pretty he's looking
pretty skinny
no red couldn't make it but i i felt bad
not having him here so he's here in um
armor stand spirit so he gets he gets to
see it still right so can you make this
thing count down from i guess nine
because you can't do ten and then you
can launch this thing
oh man yeah absolutely i can do that i
just gotta get behind there change the
setting on that and then we'll get that
going all right green i have set it to
nine and when i fire this arrow into
that pressure plate down below we're
going to start the countdown from nine
down to zero
you ready
right down there you see straight down
i had to give myself
oh there it goes
oh he started the countdown
eight
seven yeah you saved me from having to
uh shoot the the bow there
okay i think it stopped when you got off
the pressure plate here
i'll restart it goodness
okay oh that's hilarious that was
totally smooth man here it goes seven
six six
five five
four
three
two
there goes
oh oh there they go
oh very nice
all right let's get this thing in the
air so this is the moment that everyone
has been waiting for it is time to
rebuild this giant rv
right up in the sky this is exactly what
everyone's been anticipating but i have
been personally putting it off because
destroying a build
is heartbreaking enough as it is but to
rebuild that exact same thing just a
little bit higher it's it's soul
crushing however i just had to get it
done so i basically tried to replicate
it but somehow i messed up and i put the
wheels in a slightly different position
but
it really doesn't matter because the rv
is still there and it still looks
roughly the same that's the main thing
at the end of the day the major
difference this time is on the bottom
side of it i had to do a trail of fire
because this is a real rocket launching
into the air and i actually had to ask
scar what the trick was to make this
look right and he actually gave me some
really good advice so thank you arie 77
for helping me launch this rv into the
air and it really does look quite cool
it doesn't actually look so out of place
it
is complete
the rv is in the air it has taken off
maybe this is what you expected maybe
not
but
this isn't it this is this is only the
first half i actually am really happy
with how how this looks it actually
genuinely looks like it's taking off i
haven't actually managed to finish the
trail of smoke i need to work on that a
bit more but overall
i'm really happy with how it's look look
at this hippie land look at how this has
come together the barn the mushroom
the the rv flying this looks absolutely
epic
however i as i said this is not over yet
we've got
well one more stage which is why i've
asked impulse to join me he's over there
on the platform
because
there's actually two countdowns that
need to happen the one that we just had
was for getting the rv airborne so it's
this silo is now empty
and has risen above so this should
really spook the guys over at area 77 as
they will see this from pretty much
anywhere if they're over here
you can see oh my goodness you really
can see it if you're over here
that is terrifying
but there is one
more
thing and for that we're gonna spook
them again with a second countdown
and then when that hit zero
the real prank begins so i'm gonna meet
up with impulse who is right here and
we're gonna get this thing reset
okay impulse so
this countdown it wasn't just to bring
this rv in the air i'm guessing you kind
of don't know what's going on here i am
utterly confused what's going on now
okay
well everyone was kind of uh you know
guessing in the comments about what was
going to happen and most people got it
right the rv is being launched which
yeah i think i think this has gone
pretty well it looks it looks definitely
looks like it's supposed to it's
fantastic but what people aren't ready
for
is the next stage but obviously i can't
do it all in one go i've you know i
haven't got i've only got so many hours
in in the days you know so
what i need is to reset the countdown
for another
four days
four days four days
and then that's when the real prank
begins and it gives them time to be
scared as well which is oh wow it's kind
of part of the thing spooking them
that's kind of why why this whole
thing's here
so yeah
four more days of anticipation yes
[Laughter]
did you hit that wall you your face slid
down it like
splat
oh i am not as eloquent of a flyer as
you are man okay three yeah
one more oh man
four four more days four more days
everybody has to wait to find out what
this is really about oh my goodness how
do you think what do you think about
this uh
old ren
yeah yeah we forgot to ask ren
i think he nodded yeah
i see in his eyes it is
in his eyes he's enjoying it
okay when you look at this face do you
see what do you see do you see a smiley
face
or do you see a beard i see a smiley
face i see it's supposed to be a beard
it's supposed to be a beard dude
oh
it's totally a smiley face it does look
like a smiley face here we are just
judging ren he can't even stick up for
him he's he's happy he's happy that's
amazing
all right so four more days and then the
real
prank begins and i'm gonna need your
help even though you don't know what's
gonna happen i'm gonna need your help
you in okay i'm definitely in i'm
excited oh sweet
four days